Hello friends, how are you all, I hope you are doing
well, your investing journey is
going well, so today we are going to talk about
ICC
Lombard stock technical analysis,
if you subscribe to the channel and
like and share the video, then let's
discuss it in detail,
what is the situation in this stock, so as per
my understanding
[music]
stop support is at its support, you can
buy, you can buy it, you can buy it for Rs 1355 and
take the target of 1420, but if you
want a little bigger return, then you have to
buy above the level of 1420 and
keep the target almost
in the stock, you can move ahead,
tell us by commenting in the comment area, we will meet
in the next video, till then
Radhe Radhe to everyone